{
  "fileName": "Quiz Miller_Spoolman Living in the Environment 16e, Chapter, Chapter 3.pdf.txt",
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "The basic, fundamental unit of life is the",
      "choices": [
        "molecule.",
        "organism.",
        "species.",
        "cell."
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Even though it interacts with others of its kind and with the abiotic realm around it, a single living individual is best described as a/an",
      "choices": [
        "species.",
        "system.",
        "population.",
        "organism."
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "Fossil fuels are found in the",
      "choices": [
        "hydrosphere.",
        "stratosphere.",
        "geosphere.",
        "troposphere."
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "Large terrestrial regions with distinct climates and distinct species adapted to them are called",
      "choices": [
        "biomes.",
        "aquatic life zones.",
        "the biosphere.",
        "ecosystems."
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "Which of the following is not true of solar energy reaching the earth?",
      "choices": [
        "Some solar energy is recycled as high energy light.",
        "Some solar energy is captured by plants to form chemical energy.",
        "Some solar energy is absorbed by ozone in the atmosphere.",
        "Some solar energy is reflected by the atmosphere."
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "Carbon dioxide, water vapor, and ozone in the atmosphere naturally trap some of the light that reflects back from the earth\u0027s surface. The light is converted to heat, with the gases acting as insulating blankets. This natural process warms the earth enough to support life. This process is called",
      "choices": [
        "solar capital.",
        "global climate change.",
        "nutrient flow and energy cycling.",
        "the greenhouse effect."
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Think of a terrestrial forest ecosystem (we have presumably all walked in a forest). From an ecological point of view, ecosystems such as this are actually simple to understand.",
      "choices": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "Limiting factors are abiotic factors that can enhance or prevent growth of a population, even if all other factors are at or near the optimum. Which of the following would be an example of a limiting factor?",
      "choices": [
        "mate availability",
        "all of the choices",
        "water availability",
        "food availability"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "Organisms that gain their energy and nutrients from eating plants are called",
      "choices": [
        "omnivores.",
        "producers.",
        "detritivores.",
        "primary consumers."
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Organisms that gain their nutrients by breaking down organic compounds in the absence of oxygen do so by",
      "choices": [
        "transpiration.",
        "aerobic respiration.",
        "anaerobic respiration.",
        "photosynthesis."
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "Heat is a byproduct of each energy transformation in an ecosystem. Therefore, this represents a one way energy flow from the sun through the ecosystem.",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "Both energy and nutrients flow through ecosystems. Which of the following is true?",
      "choices": [
        "Without new inputs of energy and nutrients, both will eventually run out.",
        "Both energy and nutrients are biotic.",
        "Although useful energy will eventually be used up, nutrients can always be recycled.",
        "Water causes both energy and nutrients to flow throughout the system."
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "If asked to pick the model that best illustrates real-world biotic ecosystem interactions, you should pick the",
      "choices": [
        "biogeochemical cycle.",
        "food web.",
        "pyramid of energy flow.",
        "food chain."
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "Energy flow pyramids show",
      "choices": [
        "all of the choices",
        "loss of energy at each trophic level.",
        "available energy at each trophic level.",
        "why food chains cannot be too large."
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "The relationship between gross primary production (GPP), net primary production (NPP), and respiration energy (R) is",
      "choices": [
        "GPP \u003d NPP - R",
        "NPP \u003d GPP - R",
        "NPP \u003d GPP/R",
        "NPP \u003d GPP + R"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "Which of the following does not qualify as a biogeochemical cycle?",
      "choices": [
        "water",
        "nitrogen",
        "energy",
        "carbon"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "Evaporation and ________ are responsible for putting water into the atmosphere.",
      "choices": [
        "precipitation",
        "transpiration",
        "infiltration",
        "percolation"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "________ is the only significant natural process that moves carbon dioxide from the atmosphere.",
      "choices": [
        "Anaerobic respiration",
        "Photosynthesis",
        "Aerobic respiration",
        "Precipitation"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "A significant cause of natural sulfur dioxide into the atmosphere is",
      "choices": [
        "sulfur in ocean sediments.",
        "sulfur in animal tissues.",
        "volcanic eruptions.",
        "animal waste decomposition."
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 21,
      "question": "Ecosystem study primarily involving GIS (geographic information system) is usually most closely associated with",
      "choices": [
        "laboratory research.",
        "ecosystem modeling.",
        "literature review.",
        "field research."
      ],
      "correct": 3
    }
  ]
}